Your AI agent just called
a tool it shouldn't have.
Assay catches it. Exit code one.
CI blocks the deploy.
Fix the policy.
Run it again.
Green. Deterministic.
Same trace, same result, every time.
Every action your agent takes becomes a signed
event in a content-addressed evidence bundle.
Explore everything interactively.
See exactly what happened.
Merkle root, SHA-256, JCS canonicalization.
Cryptographic proof of what your agent actually did.
Attack simulation tests your gates against known vectors.
Bitflip, truncation, injection — blocked or bypassed, you'll know.
One install. No signup.
Runs offline.
cargo install assay